Sanchita K Raghuprasad

+61406924286 | sanchita_kr@outlook.com | linkedin.com/in/sanchita-kamakodu-raghuprasad | github.com/Sanchitakr

OBJECTIVE

Exploring and traversing areas of Machine Learning, Data Science and Artificial Intelligence and fathoming the awe inspiring and enriching experience as an Artificial Intelligence postgraduate. Discovering my limitations and also the positive energy of knowledge that would help me combat them through the process.

EDUCATION

University of New south Wales

Master of Information Technology, Specialising in Artificial Intelligence

Sydney, NSW, Australia Aug. 2018 – Sep 2020

Jawaharlal Nehru National College of Engineering

Bachelor of Engineering, Major - Information Science and Technology

Shimoga, Karnataka, India Aug. 2013 – May 2017

Experience

Artificial Intelligence Consultant

Meksi Pvt Ltd

Sep 2020 – Present Sydney, NSW

- Developed Google BERT model from scratch using HuggingFace, Fast API and Context Augmentation tool to refine the training data
- Contributed in refining the simulator to collect objective assessment data on the user in this case a medical student or a clinical practitioner using React-Redux Saga, Springboot, MySQL and AWS.
- \bullet With language model of BERT layered on IBM Watson assistant for efficient intent selection, increased the accuracy of the model by up to 96%
- Managed Virtual Simulator Patient project and contributed in shaping Meksi to be recognised as a unique product in the field of medical Simulators
- Explored ways to improve website interactions by User-driven analysis using HubSpot and increased the user interactions by up to 60%

Software Engineer Intern

May 2019 – Aug 2020

Sydney, NSW

InsideSherpa - Virtual Internship

- Visualisation of the transaction volume and Assessing the effect of outliers
- Monitor correlation between customer attributes, build regressions and building decision-tree prediction model
- Social Engineering Investigation- Phishing, security report writing, Digital/open source investigation
- Digital Investigation Analyse a Packet Capture file using an open source tool to identify and investigate any potential threats and open source investigations

Information Technology Consultant

Sep 2019 - Apr 2020

University of New South Wales

Sydney, NSW

- Worked on Automation testing with Cypress where Created the first automation test suite for the Ex-LIBRIS Digital Library PRIMO Application used by universities across NSW
- Designed, developed and executed automation test scripts in JavaScript and mocha using the Cypress automation tool
- Implemented a comprehensive test plan and increased the effectiveness, efficiency, and coverage of sanity testing by up to 400~%

Junior Software Engineer

Jan 2018 – Jul 2018

Renewin Technology

Bangalore, Karnataka, India

- Monitor multiple functionalities of multiple applications for a Fortune 50 company also improve functionalities and extra features requested by the client on time
- Implemented Skype chat bot using Watson Assistant to integrate daily excel time sheet with company Skype. Increases efficiency and time management by 30%
- Languages: Core Java, JavaScript, HTML, XML

Question Answering Model | TensorFlow, Google BERT, Docker, Git, Watson Assistant Oct 2020 - Nov 2020

- Developed a BERT model pre-trained on clinical and custom medical data (SQuAD 1.1)
- Implemented Bert Optimiser and Tokenizer libraries for text analysis.
- For better prediction of answers, designed custom masks in terms with length of query token.
- Implemented sliding window approach to capture the context of the paragraph which is used for training
- Trained the model on IBM Cloud Watson Machine Learning which increased the accuracy from 88% to 92% with F1 score of 0.87

Book Recommender System | Python, Flask, HTML, CSS3, Javascript, SQLite, Dash June 2020 - Aug 2020

- Developed a full-stack web application using with Flask serving a REST API with python Dash as the frontend
- Implemented GitHub OAuth to get data from user's repositories
- Visualized GitHub data to show collaboration
- Implemented agile methodology along with JIRA ticket system to carry out synchronous tasks

Movie Revenue Prediction | Pandas, numpy, Xboost regressor, sklearn, Git

Feb 2020 – Apr 2020

- Programmed data preparation for unstructured data which includes data quality assessment , feature aggregation, feature sampling, dimensionality reduction, and feature encoding
- For the model selection, implemented a Hyper-parameter grid search using the XGBoost regressor library
- Improved R² on revenue prediction by from 0.68 to 0.77, minimising correlation and by including prominent features

Technical Skills

Languages: Latex, Java, Python, C/C++, SQL (MySQL), JavaScript, HTML/CSS

Frameworks: React, Node.js, Flask

Developer Tools: GitHub, Docker, VS Code, PyCharm, IBM Watson Assistant

Libraries: pandas, NumPy, Matplotlib, Transformers (BERT)